MR. Robot Adversarial — SANS FIND EVIL! 2026
Autonomous AI cyber-defense pipeline.
The problem: AI adversaries breach in under 8 minutes.
Our pipeline: scan → triage → adversarial review → verdict, in ~30 seconds.
Three trust layers, two model families, one rule-based judge.
Scanners are deterministic. The auditor is a different model family
than the triage agent — agreement actually carries information.
Health check — providers, scanners, audit DB all online.
Sample 1: a Python bind shell. Expected verdict: MALICIOUS.
Step 1: deterministic scanners (skill, IOC, YARA, secrets) light up.
Step 2: MR. Robot (Nemotron) runs a 5-phase triage.
Step 3: Falsifier (DeepSeek) audits the triage.
ΔA = 1.0 — propagator and auditor are different families.
Verdict: MALICIOUS. Audit trail records every step.
Sample 2: a Django view with parameterized ORM. Expected: BENIGN.
The Falsifier is framework-aware: it knows Django auto-escapes
and that .filter() parameterizes — no SQL injection vector.
Verdict: BENIGN. Without the Falsifier this is a likely false alarm.
Sample 3: an obfuscated npm worm. Triage uncertain on the first pass.
Falsifier challenges the verdict → MR. Robot re-runs with the counter-argument.
Max 2 iterations — beyond that, same-family re-runs amplify error
rather than reduce it (Shehata & Li 2026).
Verdict on the worm: MALICIOUS after 2 iterations.
Accuracy on 118 ground-truth samples (99 malicious + 19 benign):
Recall 100%, Precision 97.1%, F1 0.985, FPR 15.8%.
Three false positives are listed in the report — we surface them,
we don't suppress them.
Audit trail (SANS requirement #8): every tool call logged
to SQLite WAL with verdict, confidence, ΔA, and kinship-lock flag.
github.com/Grizaceo/mr-robot-adversarial — MIT license.
Try-it-out guide: docs/try_it_out.md