MR. Robot Adversarial — SANS FIND EVIL! 2026
Autonomous AI cyber-defense pipeline.
The problem: AI adversaries breach in under 8 minutes.
We close the gap: scan → triage → adversarial review → verdict, ~30s.
Three trust layers, two model families, one rule-based judge.
(scanners deterministic, auditor different family from triage)
Health check — providers, scanners, audit DB online.
4 wired scanners: skill, ioc, yara, secrets.
Sample 1: Python bind shell. We expect MALICIOUS.
Pipeline: scanners (10 findings) → MR. Robot (gpt-oss) → synthesizer → MALICIOUS 0.97.
Sample 2: Django view with parameterized ORM. We expect BENIGN.
Falsifier refutes FPs. Final verdict: BENIGN 0.99.
Sample 7: Self-correction loop. Forced with MR_ROBOT_FORCE_FALSIFIER=1.
Triage (gpt-oss-120b) → MALICIOUS 0.97 → Falsifier (nemotron-3-ultra) → SURVIVED → ΔA=1.0, kinship_lock_risk=LOW.
Sample 8: Accuracy on 173 samples (135 malicious + 38 benign).
Accuracy 99.42%, Precision 99.26%, Recall 100%, FPR 2.63% (1 FP).
Sample 9: Audit trail — every tool call logged in SQLite with timestamps.
SANS Requirement #8 satisfied.
Repo: github.com/Grizaceo/mr-robot-adversarial
License: MIT  •  Branch: grounding-audit-competition-pass